Campus Construction; Collection ua950.005
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- New York State Normal College Architectural Blueprints, 1906-1908
  - New York State Normal College blueprint, longitudinal section. Subbasement plan, drawing number 129, 1908 January 8
- Land Requirements and Building Needs of the State of New York in the Albany Area and Acquisition by the State of the Site of the Albany Country Club, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Documents, 1961-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Construction Fund/ Edward Durell Stove Planning Correspondence 1961/1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Evolution of an Architect by Edward Durell Stone 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Arena Theater, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Planning, General, 1962-1964; 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- New Campus, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Edward Durell Stone, SUNYA Scrapbook (Photocopy of the original courtesy of the office of Dennis Sebeveal), 1962-1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Progress Report on SUNY 1964 Master Plan, Correspondence, 1962-1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Campus Construction Progress Reports Walter Tisdale #1-237, 1963-1974 (Box 1, Folder 13, 37)
  - Campus Progress Report No. 1, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 May 2
  - Campus Progress Report No. 2, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 May 7
  - Campus Progress Report No. 3, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 May 22
  - Campus Progress Report No. 4, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 May 28
  - Campus Progress Report No. 5, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 June 20
  - Campus Progress Report No. 6, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 June 26
  - Campus Progress Report No. 7, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 June 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 8, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 July 26
  - Campus Progress Report No. 9, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 August 1
  - Campus Progress Report No. 10, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 August 13
  - Campus Progress Report No. 11, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 September 3
  - Campus Progress Report No. 12, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 September 13
  - Campus Progress Report No. 13, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 September 19
  - Campus Progress Report No. 15, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 October 8
  - Campus Progress Report No. 16, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 October 22
  - Campus Progress Report No. 17, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 October 24
  - Campus Progress Report No. 18, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 October 25
  - Campus Progress Report No. 19, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 October 29
  - Campus Progress Report No. 20, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 November 4
  - Campus Progress Report No. 21, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 November 6
  - Campus Progress Report No. 22, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 November 14
  - Campus Progress Report No. 23, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 November 21
  - Campus Progress Report No. 24, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 December 3
  - Campus Progress Report No. 25, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1963 December 18
  - Campus Progress Report No. 26, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 January 3
  - Campus Progress Report No. 27, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 January 6
  - Campus Progress Report No. 28, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 January 9
  - Campus Progress Report No. 29, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 January 15
  - Campus Progress Report No. 30, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 January 21
  - Campus Progress Report No. 31, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 January 24
  - Campus Progress Report No. 32, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 February 3
  - Campus Progress Report No. 33, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 February 4
  - Campus Progress Report No. 34, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 February 11
  - Campus Progress Report No. 35, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 February 21
  - Campus Progress Report No. 36, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 February 26
  - Campus Progress Report No. 37, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 March 3
  - Campus Progress Report No. 38, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 March 6
  - Campus Progress Report No. 39, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 March 17
  - Campus Progress Report No. 40, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 March 24
  - Campus Progress Report No. 41, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 April 8
  - Campus Progress Report No. 42, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 April 14
  - Campus Progress Report No. 43, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 April 21
  - Campus Progress Report No. 44, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 April 30
  - Campus Progress Report No. 45, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 May 12
  - Campus Progress Report No. 46, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 May 19
  - Campus Progress Report No. 47, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 June 2
  - Campus Progress Report No. 48, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 June 11
  - Campus Progress Report No. 49, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 June 26
  - Campus Progress Report No. 50, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 July 1
  - Campus Progress Report No. 51, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 July 20
  - Campus Progress Report No. 52, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 July 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 53, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 August 7
  - Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1965 April 19
  - Campus Progress Report No. 54, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1964 November 6
  - Campus Progress Report No. 55, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1965 May 4
  - Campus Progress Report No. 56, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1965 June 9
  - Campus Progress Report No. 57, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1965 June 11
  - Campus Progress Report No. 58, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1965 June 28
  - Campus Progress Report No. 59, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1965 July 28
  - Campus Progress Report No. 60, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1965 September 29
  - Campus Progress Report No. 61, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1965 October 6
  - Campus Progress Report No. 62, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1965 October 18
  - Campus Progress Report No. 63, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1965 October 21
  - Campus Progress Report No. 64, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1965 October 29
  - Campus Progress Report No. 65, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1965 December 3
  - Campus Progress Report No. 66, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 January 10
  - Campus Progress Report No. 67, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 January 28
  - Campus Progress Report No. 68, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 February 15
  - Campus Progress Report No. 69, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 March 1
  - Campus Progress Report No. 70, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 August 22
  - Campus Progress Report No. 71, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 September 12
  - Campus Progress Report No. 72, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 September 15
  - Campus Progress Report No. 73, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 September 30
  - Campus Progress Report No. 74, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 October 18
  - Campus Progress Report No. 75, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 October 26
  - Campus Progress Report No. 76, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 November 9
  - Campus Progress Report No. 77, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 November 17
  - Campus Progress Report No. 78, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 December 19
  - Campus Progress Report No. 79, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1966 December 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 80, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 February 21
  - Campus Progress Report No. 81, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 February 21
  - Campus Progress Report No. 82, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 March 1
  - Campus Progress Report No. 83, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 March 23
  - Campus Progress Report No. 84, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 March 15
  - Campus Progress Report No. 85, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 April 24
  - Campus Progress Report No. 86, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 April 28
  - Campus Progress Report No. 87, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 June 2
  - Campus Progress Report No. 88, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 June 12
  - Campus Progress Report No. 89, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 June 21
  - Campus Progress Report No. 90, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 July 10
  - Campus Progress Report No. 91, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 July 14
  - Campus Progress Report No. 92, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 July 29
  - Campus Progress Report No. 93, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 August 9
  - Campus Progress Report No. 94, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 August 10
  - Campus Progress Report No. 95, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 August 21
  - Campus Progress Report No. 96, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 August 23
  - Campus Progress Report No. 97, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 September 7
  - Campus Progress Report No. 98, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 September 7
  - Campus Progress Report No. 99, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 September 8
  - Campus Progress Report No. 100, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 September 12
  - Comprehensive Campus Plan Report, 1967 September 13
  - Campus Progress Report No. 101, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 September 19
  - Campus Progress Report No. 102, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 September 25
  - Campus Progress Report No. 103, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 October 2
  - Campus Progress Report No. 104, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 October 4
  - Campus Progress Report No. 105, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 October 5
  - Campus Progress Report No. 106, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 October 24
  - Campus Progress Report No. 107, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 October 26
  - Campus Progress Report No. 108, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 November 1
  - Campus Progress Report No. 109, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 November 6
  - Campus Progress Report No. 110, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 November 15
  - Campus Progress Report No. 111, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 November 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 112, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 December 7
  - Campus Progress Report No. 113, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 December 15
  - Campus Progress Report No. 114, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 December 18
  - Campus Progress Report No. 115, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1967 December 21
  - Campus Progress Report No. 116, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 January 25
  - Campus Progress Report No. 117, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 January 29
  - Campus Progress Report No. 118, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 January 30
  - Campus Progress Report No. 119, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 February 28
  - Campus Progress Report No. 120, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 April 2
  - Campus Progress Report No. 121, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 April 12
  - Campus Progress Report No. 122, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 April 24
  - Campus Progress Report No. 123, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 April 24
  - Campus Progress Report No. 124, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 May 10
  - Campus Progress Report No. 125, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 May 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 126, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 June 6
  - Campus Progress Report No. 127, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 June 19
  - Campus Progress Report No. 128, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 June 19
  - Campus Progress Report No. 129, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 June 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 130, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 July 2
  - Campus Progress Report No. 131, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 August 13
  - Campus Progress Report No. 132, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 September 13
  - Campus Progress Report No. 133, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 October 8
  - Campus Progress Report No. 134, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 October 30
  - Campus Progress Report No. 135 (a), Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 November 14
  - Campus Progress Report No. 135 (b), Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 November 25
  - Campus Progress Report No. 136, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 November 26
  - Campus Progress Report No. 137 (a), Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 November 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 137 (b), Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 December 11
  - Campus Progress Report No. 137 (c), Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 December 6
  - Campus Progress Report No. 138, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 December 6
  - Campus Progress Report No. 139, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1968 December 18
  - Campus Progress Report No. 140, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1969 January 13
  - Campus Progress Report No. 141, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1969 February 19
  - Campus Progress Report No. 142, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1969 March 4
  - Campus Progress Report No. 143, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1969 March 19
  - Campus Progress Report No. 144, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1969 April 1
  - Campus Progress Report No. 145, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1969 April 11
  - Campus Progress Report No. 146, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1969 April 29
  - Campus Progress Report No. 147, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1969 May 23
  - Campus Progress Report No. 148, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Evan R. Collins, 1969 June 24
  - Campus Progress Report No. 149, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Allan A. Kuusisto, 1969 August 13
  - Campus Progress Report No. 150, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Allan A. Kuusisto, 1969 September 29
  - Campus Progress Report No. 151, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Allan A. Kuusisto, 1969 November 25
  - Campus Progress Report No. 152, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Allan A. Kuusisto, 1969 December 5
  - Campus Progress Report No. 153, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Allan A. Kuusisto, 1969 December 10
  - Campus Progress Report No. 154, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Allan A. Kuusisto, 1970 February 4
  - Campus Progress Report No. 155, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Allan A. Kuusisto, 1970 March 10
  - Campus Progress Report No. 156, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Allan A. Kuusisto, 1970 May 28
  - Campus Progress Report No. 157, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Allan A. Kuusisto, 1970 June 1
  - Campus Progress Report No. 158, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Allan A. Kuusisto, 1970 June 4
  - Campus Progress Report No. 159, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Allan A. Kuusisto, 1970 June 9
  - Campus Progress Report No. 160, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Allan A. Kuusisto, 1970 June 10
  - Campus Progress Report No. 161, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Charles O'Reilly and others, 1970 June 26
  - Campus Progress Report No. 162, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1970 July 2
  - Campus Progress Report No. 163, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1970 July 23
  - Campus Progress Report No. 164, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1970 August 19
  - Campus Progress Report No. 165, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1970 August 20
  - Campus Progress Report No. 166, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1970 September 16
  - Campus Progress Report No. 167, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1970 December 2
  - Campus Progress Report No. 168, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1970 December 22
  - Campus Progress Report No. 169, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1970 December 23
  - Campus Progress Report No. 170, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 January 22
  - Campus Progress Report No. 171 (a), Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 February 16
  - Campus Progress Report No. 171 (b), Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 April 16
  - Campus Progress Report No. 172, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 April 20
  - Campus Progress Report No. 173, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 June 9
  - Campus Progress Report No. 174, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 July 9
  - Campus Progress Report No. 175, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 July 9
  - Campus Progress Report No. 176, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 August 12
  - Campus Progress Report No. 177, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 August 20
  - Campus Progress Report No. 178, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 August 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 179, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 September 15
  - Campus Progress Report No. 180, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 October 5
  - Campus Progress Report No. 181, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 October 13
  - Campus Progress Report No. 182, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 October 14
  - Campus Progress Report No. 183, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 November 3
  - Campus Progress Report No. 184, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 November 10
  - Campus Progress Report No. 185, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1971 November 17
  - Campus Progress Report No. 186, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1972 January 25
  - Campus Progress Report No. 187, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1972 January 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 188, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1972 February 18
  - Campus Progress Report No. 189, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1972 April 21
  - Campus Progress Report No. 190, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1972 April 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 191, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1972 May 10
  - Campus Progress Report No. 192, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1972 June 1
  - Campus Progress Report No. 193 (a), Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1972 June 5
  - Campus Progress Report No. 193 (b), Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to President Louis T. Benezet, 1972 June 8
  - Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 June 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 194, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 June 28
  - Campus Progress Report No. 195, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 June 30
  - Campus Progress Report No. 196, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 July 7
  - Campus Progress Report No. 198, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 July 19
  - Campus Progress Report No. 199, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 August 11
  - Campus Progress Report No. 200, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 August 22